Guide to the Gordon Moore Papers M1965
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Chronological Files, 1958-2003
  - Sub-Series I: Correspondence, Minutes and Other Material affiliated with Gordon Moore, 1958-2003
    - Stanford University Computer System Laboratory Colloquium re: Very Large Scale Integration Industry Trends, Technological and Economic - Map, Correspondence [Originally in Box 49, Folder 9], December 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute Annual Forecast Dinner - Presentation Slides re: Capital Spending, Presentation Outline, Correspondence, Program, Notes, Badge, Presentation Outline of Michael Ciesinski re: Electronic Industry Food Chain, Articles [Originally in Box 50, Folder 1], December 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Bay Area Council Outlook Conference - Correspondence, Program, Speech Outline re: Can US Compete in Semiconductors?, Research Paper re: National Performance Goals by Bill Honig, Newsletter [Originally in Box 50, Folder 3], January 1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. Advanced Micro Devices - Reports, Correspondence, Notes, Presentation Slides, Newsletter [Originally in Box 51, Folder 2], 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Supercomputer Export Control Hearings - Notes, Testimony of the Commerce Department’s Proposed Definition of Supercomputer, Statement of Dr. Irving Wladawsky-Berger of IBM Corporation, Comments on Supercomputer by David Anderson, Amdahl Corp., Comments on Supercomputer by Hitachi Data System Corp., Statement of Larry Tesler, Apple Computer, Inc., Testimony of Stephen Campbell, FPS Computing Inc. [Originally in Box 51, Folder 3], February 1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - American Electronics Association Systems/USA Management Issues Conference - Correspondence, Program, Presentation Slides, Presentation Outline re: Competing with Japan [Originally in Box 51, Folder 4], February 1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. Puerto Rico Systems Site Manufacturing T-8 Building - Agenda, Article [Originally in Box 51, Folder 5], February 1990 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Intel Corp. IBM Executive Quality Excellence Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Agenda [Originally in Box 51, Folder 6], February 1990 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Dataquest Booklets re: Worldwide Market Share Estimates and Semiconductor Revenue and Shipment Forecast [Originally in Box 51, Folder 7], 1990 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - San Jose Symphony Orchestra CEO Night - Correspondence, Lists [Originally in Box 52, Folder 3], March 1990 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Intel Corp. Financial Meetings in Europe - Presentation Slides re: Architect of the Microcomputer Revolution, Article [Originally in Box 52, Folder 4], March 1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Intel Corp. Annual Shareholders Meeting re: Health of California Electronics Industry Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow - Speech Outline, Minutes of BOD May Meeting, Transcript, Agenda [Originally in Box 52, Folder 5], May 1990 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Presentation Slides re: Strategic Long Range Planning ‘90, Minutes, Agenda, Capital Project Authorizations [Originally in Box 52, Folder 6], May 1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - IEEE Symposium on Very Large Scale Integration Technology re: Semiconductor Industry of the Next Decade - Presentation Slides, Notes, Correspondence, Program, Digest of Technical Papers [Originally in Box 52, Folder 7], June 1990 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - New Mexico Chamber of Commerce - Notes, Speech Outline, Correspondence [Originally in Box 52, Folder 8], June 1990 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Asilomar Conference - Presentation Slides, Overhead Transparencies, Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 53, Folder 1], July 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Hot Chips Conference Tribute to Robert Noyce - Notes, Program, Correspondence [Originally in Box 53, Folder 2], August 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Robert Noyce Obituary - Physics Today Magazine, January 1991 issue, Correspondence re: Robert Noyce Fellowship Fund, Obituary [Originally in Box 53, Folder 5], September 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. K-12 Education Meeting - Correspondence, Article, Memo Pad with Notes re: High School Chemistry Class [Originally in Box 53, Folder 7], October 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Semiconductor Research Corp. Techcon ‘90 Meeting re: Challenges for the ‘90s - Program, Notes re: An Industry View, Presentation Slides re: Semiconductors: Survival by Being Involved, Correspondence [Originally in Box 53, Folder 8], October 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Santa Clara University Breakfast Meeting - Correspondence [Originally in Box 53, Folder 9], October 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. Distributor Presidents Conference - Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: Silicon Valley, Notes [Originally in Box 53, Folder 10], October 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - National Medal of Technology - Correspondence, Articles, News clippings [Originally in Box 54, Folder 2], November 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - University of California, Berkeley CCC Conference (Corporate Capabilities and Competitiveness) - Newsletter, Correspondence, Brochure, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides, Notes, Presentation Outline, Research Papers by David J. Teece, and Richard Nelson, Agenda [Originally in Box 54, Folder 5], December 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Presentation Slides, Correspondence re: Dataquest Lunch and Moore’s Law [Originally in Box 55, Folder 2], January 1991 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - National Engineers Week, Discover E Program, Wilcox High School - Correspondence, Programs, Poster, Newsletter [Originally in Box 55, Folder 3], February 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Think Tank Meeting - Presentation Slides re: Microelectronics [Originally in Box 55, Folder 4], February 1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Caltech Earnest C. Watson Lecture - Notes, Presentation Slides re: An Industry in Transition, Speech Outline, Correspondence [Originally in Box 55, Folder 5], March 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley Lecture and Noyce Fellowship - Presentation Slides, Notes, Correspondence, Program, Memo Pad re: Microelectronics Industry in 90’s, Map [Originally in Box 55, Folder 7], April 1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Intel Corp. Tax Meeting – Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides re: Who is going to build all these chips?, Notes [Originally in Box 55, Folder 8], April 1991 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Leaders for Manufacturing Symposium - Presentation Slides re: Effecting Change in Semiconductor Manufacturing, Pamphlet, Notes, Report on Intel Corp. [Originally in Box 55, Folder 9], April 1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Boston Society of Security Analysts Meeting - Presentation Slides re: Architect of the Microcomputer Revolution, Correspondence, Brochure [Originally in Box 56, Folder 1], April 1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - San Jose State University School of Business Annual Banquet - Booklet, Notes, Correspondence [Originally in Box 56, Folder 2], April 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Presentation Slides, Correspondence, Capital Project Authorizations, Agenda [Originally in Box 56, Folder 3], May 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Intel Corp. Annual Stockholders Meeting - Meeting Transcript, Correspondence, Agenda, Presentation Slides re: Systems Group Update by Frank Gill [Originally in Box 56, Folder 5], May 1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Charlie E. Sporck’s Retirement - Speech Notes [Originally in Box 56, Folder 6], 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Caltech Dedication of Intel Touchstone DELTA System - Pamphlets, Correspondence, Notes, Program, Agenda, Product brochures, Presentation Slides re: i860 Family 1991 Rollout Plan [Originally in Box 56, Folder 7], May 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Computerworld Smithsonian Awards Program re: Price Waterhouse Information Technology Leadership Award for Lifetime Achievement for Robert Noyce - Brochure, Correspondence, Programs, Newsletter [Originally in Box 56, Folder 8], June 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. i860 XR and XP Supercomputing Microprocessors (N11) Product Announcement - Correspondence, Press Release, Presentation Slides, Speech Notes [Originally in Box 56, Folder 9], June 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - National Academy of Engineering Linking Trade and Technology Policies Symposium and Symposium Publication - Correspondence, Notes, Program, Memo Pad, Opening Chapter Drafts of Linking Trade and Technology Policies: An International Comparison of the Policies of Industrialized Nations by Martha Caldwell Harris and Gordon Moore, Research Papers by Hajime Karatsu, Paul Krugman, Laura D’Andrea Tyson, David B. Yoffie, David C. Mowery, Paolo Guerrieri (1 of 4) [Originally in Box 57, Folder 1], June 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - National Academy of Engineering Linking Trade and Technology Policies Symposium and Symposium Publication - Draft of the symposium publication, Correspondence (2 of 4) [Originally in Box 57, Folder 2], June 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - National Academy of Engineering Linking Trade and Technology Policies Symposium Steering Committee - Correspondence, Agendas, Memo Pad, Notes, Article (3 of 4) [Originally in Box 57, Folder 3], June 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - National Academy of Engineering Linking Trade and Technology Policies Symposium Research Papers by Paul Krugman, Laura D’Andrea Tyson, David B. Yoffie, David C. Mowery, Paolo Guerrieri (4 of 4) [Originally in Box 57, Folder 4], June 1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Agenda, Capital Project Authorizations, Minutes [Originally in Box 58, Folder 2], July 1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - California Landmark Dedication for Robert Noyce - Correspondence, Presentation Notes [Originally in Box 58, Folder 4], August 1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - IEEE Computer Magazine, 40th Anniversary Issue re: Semiconductor Technology Reaches Middle Age - Correspondence, Computer Magazine, issue September 1990 [Originally in Box 58, Folder 7], 1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Human Resources Summit re: Intel Strategic Long Range Planning and Q&A’s on HR’s role - Agenda, Articles, Presentation Slides, Correspondence [Originally in Box 58, Folder 8], September 1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Microcontamination Conference 91, San Jose Convention Center - Presentation Slides re: We’ve Come a Long Way and Have a Long Way to Go, Correspondence, Pamphlets, Presentation Outline, Notes, Program [Originally in Box 58, Folder 9], October 1991 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Intel Corp. Distributor Presidents’ Conference - Presentation Slides, Correspondence, Speech Outline re: Our Industry in Retrospect [Originally in Box 59, Folder 2], October 1991 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute International Trade Partners Conference re: Strategies for Global Cooperation and Competition - Presentation Slides re: Our Changing Industry, Correspondence, Notes, Pamphlet, Presentation Outlines (1 of 2) [Originally in Box 59, Folder 3], November 1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute International Trade Partners Conference re: Strategies for Global Cooperation and Competition - Binder Program, Executive Summary Report (2 of 2) [Originally in Box 59, Folder 4], November 1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. London Analyst Meeting - Notes, Presentation Slides re: Business Strategy, Articles, Pamphlet, Supercomputer Product Overview re: Paragon XP/S, Supercomputer Market Agendas [Originally in Box 59, Folder 6], December 1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Overhead Transparencies, Agenda, Capital Project Authorizations, Minutes [Originally in Box 60, Folder 2], January 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Intel Foundation, SC 9 Auditorium - Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 60, Folder 4], January 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - National Engineers Week, Discover E Program, Wilcox High School - Correspondence, Brochures, Comic Book [Originally in Box 60, Folder 6], February 1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - National Academy of Engineering (NAE) Workshop re: Removing the Barriers to World Class Manufacturing - Brochure, Correspondence, Pamphlets, Presentation Slides re: Taking Next Steps: A US Technology Strategy, Reports, NAE The Bridge Publication, Vol. 21, No 4. [Originally in Box 60, Folder 7], March 1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association/ Semiconductor Research Corp. Washington Conference - Correspondence, Presentation Slides re: The Cowboys Who Became Settlers: Semiconductor Industry Surviving by Becoming Involved [Originally in Box 60, Folder 8], March 1992 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Economic Strategy Institute Conference re: Economics and Strategy - Correspondence, Program, Overhead Transparencies, Memo Pad, Notes, Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Semiconductors: Survival By Being Involved, Cowboys Who Became Settlers [Originally in Box 61, Folder 1], March 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Royal Swedish Academy of Engineering Sciences (IVA) Delegation to Universities and Companies in California - Program, Pamphlets re: Uppsala University, Brochures, Correspondence, Agenda, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 61, Folder 5], April 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - National Academy of Engineering Robert Noyce Memorial Tribute - Tribute Article, Correspondence, Photocopied Articles re: Robert Noyce [Originally in Box 61, Folder 6], April 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute Honorary Doctorate of Engineering Degree -Correspondence, Newsletter, Research Abstracts re: Rensselaer Center for Integrated Electronics, Pamphlets, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 62, Folder 2], May 1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Washington Office of Management and Budget Briefing - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies, Presentation Slides re: Making America Competitive Again [Originally in Box 62, Folder 4], June 1992 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - JEMI (Joint Equipment Manufacturers Initiative) Meeting (French Vendor) - Presentation Slides, Correspondence, Semiconductor Equipment and Materials Institute Conference 1991 Presentation Notes, Agenda, Product Brochures, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 62, Folder 6], June 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Columbia Institute, Inland Empire Economic Summit: Stimulating Balanced Growth and Creating Jobs, Congressman George E. Brown, Jr. - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Remaining Competitive in Changing World, Correspondence, Notes, Agenda [Originally in Box 62, Folder 8], July 1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Silicon Valley Personal Computer Design Conference (SVPC) - Presentation Slides re: The Force to Innovate, Correspondence, Program [Originally in Box 63, Folder 1], August 1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. Board of Directors Meeting - Correspondence, Agenda, Capital Project Authorizations, Overhead Transparencies, Minutes [Originally in Box 63, Folder 2], September 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Governor Pete Wilson Visit re: Expansion of Semiconductor Manufacturing Plant, D2 - Presentation Outline, News Release, Notes [Originally in Box 63, Folder 3], October 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Semiconductor Technology Workshop - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Moving to a Single Roadmap, Correspondence, Notes, Agenda [Originally in Box 63, Folder 5], November 1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Clinton Economic Conference (of President-Elect and Vice President-Elect) - Correspondence, Agenda, Presentation Slides, Report re: Technology: Engine of Economic Growth from Clinton-Gore Campaign, Position Papers from American Electronics Association and Semiconductor Industry Association, Research Paper re: National Economic Strategy by Bill Clinton [Originally in Box 63, Folder 6], December 1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. Washington DC Meetings re: Semiconductor Industry Association Briefing and A Business Roundtable: An Exchange of Key Business and Public Policy Issues with the Women Members of Congress - Presentation Slides, Overhead Transparencies re: Making America Competitive Again and Semiconductor Technology Strategy, Program [Originally in Box 64, Folder 1], February 1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Harvard Business School Symposium re: The Future of Industrial Research - Agenda, Correspondence, Notes, Presentation Outline, Speech Transcript, Research Papers by Richard S. Rosenbloom, David A. Hounshell, Dorothy Leonard-Barton, Edith Wilson, John Doyle, Nathan Rosenberg, Richard R. Nelson, David C. Mowery, David J. Teece, Mark B. Myers [Originally in Box 64, Folder 2], February 1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - IEEE John Fritz Medal - Correspondence, Program, Invitation [Originally in Box 64, Folder 4], February 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara Industrial Forum and Research Review re: Research and Semiconductor Industry - Correspondence, Presentation Slides, Presentation Outline, Agenda [Originally in Box 64, Folder 5], March 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - American Physical Society Meeting - Notes, Presentation Slides re: Outlook for Very Large Scale Integration: Will the Balloon Burst?, Program, Presentation Outline, Correspondence, Report re: Microprocessor Technology by P.A. Gargini and G. H. Parker [Originally in Box 64, Folder 6], March 1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - American Physical Society Meeting - Overhead Transparencies re: Semiconductor Quantum Devices: The Search for the Next Transistor by Richard E. Howard, AT&T Bell Labs [Originally in Box 64, Folder 7], March 1993 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Intel Corp. Programmable Logic Devices Meeting - Correspondence, Product Pamphlet, Presentation Slides, Reports re: User-Programmable Logic [Originally in Box 64, Folder 7], March 1993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Intel Corp. VIP Dinner - Correspondence, Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 65, Folder 2], May 1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Joint Venture Silicon Valley Meeting - Presentation Outlines [Originally in Box 65, Folder 4], June 1993 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Joint Venture Silicon Valley Meeting Binder - Implementation Plans [Originally in Box 65, Folder 5], June 1993 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Computerworld Smithsonian Award re: MCI Information Technology Leadership Award for Innovation - Correspondence [Originally in Box 65, Folder 6], June 1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Very Large Scale Integration Multilevel Interconnection Conference - Presentation Slides re: Outlook for VLSI: Will the Balloon Burst?, Program, Correspondence [Originally in Box 65, Folder 7], June 1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Solectron Corp. Meeting - Presentation Outline, Correspondence [Originally in Box 65, Folder 9], July 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Intel Supercomputer Systems Division Meeting with Senator Mark O. Hatfield - Correspondence, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 66, Folder 3], August 1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - American Electronics Association 50th Anniversary Gala re: Medal of Achievement to Gordon Moore and Andrew Grove - Presentation Outline, Correspondence [Originally in Box 66, Folder 4], September 1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Microelectronics Journal - Correspondence, Article re: A Quarter of a Century of Microelectronics, Notes [Originally in Box 66, Folder 5], September 1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference - Presentation Slides, Presentation Outline re: Which Semiconductor Industry, Transcript, Brochure, Correspondence [Originally in Box 66, Folder 8], October 1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry Conference Binder - Program, Agenda, Presentation Slides [Originally in Box 67, Folder 1], October 1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University, School of Business, Jack McDonald’s Class - Notes, Overhead Transparencies [Originally in Box 67, Folder 2], October 1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Intel Corp. Flash Technology Update and Product Introduction - Presentation Outline, Presentation Slides re: Flash Technology Update and Smaller, Lighter, Longer - Lasting Mobile PCs [Originally in Box 67, Folder 4], October 1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - BRIE (The Berkeley Roundtable on the International Economy, University of California, Berkeley) Technology Summit re: Clinton Administration’s Technology Policy and Economic Investment Plans - Agenda, Article, Correspondence, Program, Notes, Reports, Pamphlets [Originally in Box 67, Folder 5], November 1993 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Caltech Management Association - Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 67, Folder 7], January 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Microelectronics Journal re: A Quarter of a Century of Microelectronics - Articles [Originally in Box 67, Folder 8], January 1994 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Caltech Ground Breaking Dinner - Transcripts, Presentation Outline re: The Accidental Entrepreneur, Engineering and Science Article, Floppy Disk, Correspondence [Originally in Box 68, Folder 1], March 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Intel Corp. Financial Accounting Standards Board (FASB) re: Stock Options - Minutes, Booklet, Correspondence, Testimony Outline, Research Papers, Notes, Articles, Reports, Agenda, Brochure (1 of 3) [Originally in Box 68, Folder 4], March 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Intel Corp. Financial Accounting Standards Board (FASB) re: Stock Options -Correspondence, Testimony Outline, Research Papers, Notes, Articles, Reports, Agenda, Brochure (2 of 3) [Originally in Box 68, Folder 5], March 1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Nikkei Interview with Gordon E. Moore - Transcripts, Floppy Disk [Originally in Box 69, Folder 2], June-September 1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Jay Pinson Roast - Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 69, Folder 3], June 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University, Center for Economic Research Conference re: Growth and Development: The Economics of 21st Century - Correspondence, Program, Research Papers by Ralph Landau, Thomas J. Campbell, Daniel P. Kessler, George B. Shepherd [Originally in Box 69, Folder 4], June 1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Santa Clara County Manufacturing Group Press Conference - Presentation Outline, Report re: Managing Chemical Releases, Graphs, Article, Correspondence [Originally in Box 69, Folder 6], July 1994 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Robertson Stephens Semiconductor Conference - Brochures, Presentation Slides re: A Wise Investment, Correspondence, Booklet, Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 69, Folder 7], July 1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Intel Corp. Intel Technology Journal [Originally in Box 173], Fall 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Intel Corp. D2P3 (Santa Clara Microchip Factory) Expansion Announcement and Governor Pete Wilson Endorsement - Presentation Outline, Correspondence, Press Releases [Originally in Box 70, Folder 2], October 1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Intel Corp. American Electronics Association Analysts Meeting - Correspondence [Originally in Box 70, Folder 3], October 1994 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Semiconductor Industry Association Forecast and Award Dinner re: Robert Noyce Award - Presentation Outline, Notes, Presentation Slides, Newsletter, Program [Originally in Box 70, Folder 4], October 1994 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - California Manufacturing Association Manufacturer of the Year Award - Program, Presentation Outline [Originally in Box 70, Folder 5], 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Gordon Bell Essay re: Network and Nodes: A View of Computing in 2000+ [Originally in Box 70, Folder 6], October 1994 (Box 29, Folder 5)